<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
      <title>General - Geoloqi Community</title>
      <link>http://community.geoloqi.com/categories/general/feed.rss</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 15 14:25:12 -0800</pubDate>
         <description>General - Geoloqi Community</description>
   <language>en-CA</language>
   <atom:link href="/discussions/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
   <item>
      <title>Understanding Trigger Callbacks</title>
      <link>http://community.geoloqi.com/discussion/209/understanding-trigger-callbacks</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2013 10:06:23 -0700</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>geografa</dc:creator>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">209@/discussions</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<span style="font-family: Arial, Verdana; font-size: small;">I'm trying to understand how the trigger callbacks work. I have a trigger on a place with a callback url that I'm trying to record the json that is passed to it. The actual callback is working&nbsp;(I can run it with trigger/run/:id)&nbsp;but I'm not understanding how the json is passed to the callback. I would like to take some of the info from the json and record it to a db. The php code looks something like this:</span><div><br /></div><div><div><span>// Check connection</span></div><div><span style="font-family: Courier New; font-size: small;">if (mysqli_connect_errno())</span></div><div><span style="font-family: Courier New; font-size: small;">&nbsp; {</span></div><div><span style="font-family: Courier New; font-size: small;">&nbsp; echo "Failed to connect to MySQL: " . mysqli_connect_error();</span></div><div><span style="font-family: Courier New; font-size: small;">&nbsp; }</span></div><div><span style="font-family: Courier New; font-size: small;"><b>// Grabs the json here</b></span></div><div><span style="font-family: Courier New; font-size: small;"><b>$request_body = file_get_contents('php://input');</b></span></div><div><span style="font-family: Courier New; font-size: small;"><b>$json = json_decode($request_body, true);</b></span></div><div><span style="font-family: Courier New; font-size: small;"><b>$name = $json["post"]["user"]["user_id"];</b></span></div><div><span style="font-family: Courier New; font-size: small;"><br /></span></div><div><span style="font-family: Courier New; font-size: small;">$sql = "INSERT INTO table1 VALUES (NULL, '$name')";</span></div><div><span style="font-family: Courier New; font-size: small;">mysqli_query($con,$sql);</span></div><div><span style="font-family: Courier New; font-size: small;">$result = mysqli_query($con,"SELECT * FROM table1");</span></div><div><span style="font-family: Courier New; font-size: small;">while($row = mysqli_fetch_array($result))</span></div><div><span style="font-family: Courier New; font-size: small;">&nbsp; {</span></div><div><span style="font-family: Courier New; font-size: small;">&nbsp; echo $row['id'] . ". User: " . $row['username'];</span></div><div><span style="font-family: Courier New; font-size: small;">&nbsp; echo "&lt;br&gt;";</span></div><div><span style="font-family: Courier New; font-size: small;">&nbsp; }</span></div><div><span style="font-family: Courier New; font-size: small;">mysqli_close($con)</span><span>;</span></div></div><div><br /></div><div><span>I'm assuming when the trigger is run, the json is passed to the callback but I'm not getting any records showing. Any help understanding how it works is appreciated!</span></div>]]></description>
   </item>
   <item>
      <title>A list for best geofence radius for specific speed?</title>
      <link>http://community.geoloqi.com/discussion/3212/a-list-for-best-geofence-radius-for-specific-speed</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2013 19:00:06 -0700</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>dr2391</dc:creator>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3212@/discussions</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[I was wondering if there was any kind of list that showed the statistics on geofence trigger accuracy at different speeds. Something like:<div><br /></div><div>100m walking = 90%&nbsp;</div><div>100m 10mph = 80%</div><div>100m 20mph = 50%</div><div>....</div><div><br /></div><div>i know ^ would be alot of work but is there any general info about radius and speed and if not, is anyone interested in starting one?</div>]]></description>
   </item>
   <item>
      <title>iOS geotracking</title>
      <link>http://community.geoloqi.com/discussion/208/ios-geotracking</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2013 08:01:35 -0700</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>jDcg41kemx87Yr7t</dc:creator>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">208@/discussions</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Hi, <br />I'm developing an app that has to compare its own position to the position of other device in an aleatory moment, depending on the distance between them the app has to do something or not. In the Android version, the position of the device is sent to the app, using a push notification, the app calculates the distance between the smartphone and the received one and if it has to do something show a concrete screen of the app. In the case of iOS, I haven't found a way to send a push notification to the app without the interaction of the user, so the solution I have think of is to send the position of the smartphone to a server and calculate the distance there, if the distance between them says that we have to do something then send a push notification to the iPhone. For that it is important to make a good geotracking of the iOS device, even in background. Can I make this with geoloqi? I have been reading the web page and it seems that nowdays we can't use it to do geotracking in iOS... am i right? can anyone suggest a way to go ahead with the task i am explaining?<br /><br />thanks!<br />]]></description>
   </item>
   <item>
      <title>Geoloqi and the real problem .. The guide</title>
      <link>http://community.geoloqi.com/discussion/202/geoloqi-and-the-real-problem-..-the-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 00:38:59 -0700</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Cianfro</dc:creator>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">202@/discussions</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Hello to All <br /><br />I create a simply app whit appcelerator ( titanium ) .... But i adding Geoloqi ... And now ????? I haven't documentation but a app Dinodeals o.O ( i go to the app store and have a big news Dino Deals don't disponible for download in my Country Italy ) <br /><br />.... Ok i open the app i read, I change the code but the app runnyng whit RUBY ( o my good ) i don't know ruby and the server for runnyng ... =( <br /><br />It's possible a easy guide ??? <br /><br />It's possible convert ruby on PHP ??<br /> <br />My app is very simple the people passing on plaza and push service lanch the info ... But this is very difficult whitout never guide ]]></description>
   </item>
   <item>
      <title>Concept Help Request</title>
      <link>http://community.geoloqi.com/discussion/183/concept-help-request</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 12:06:43 -0700</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>bp4151</dc:creator>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">183@/discussions</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[All,<div><br /></div><div>I am having a hard time trying to figure out how to overcome an issue I am having with a mobile app. I need multiple mobile users to be able to subscribe to a single layer, and allow those users to create places and triggers on that layer. Aaron informed me that layers are not public read/write, so I would need to create a bridge API to take the requests from the various mobile users and post their requests to Geoloqi through the API.&nbsp;</div><div><br /></div><div>Quest<b>i</b>on: What token/client/secret combination will allow me to do this? I used the console to create an application layer, and the application token in the bridge API and was able to post a message broadcast without error, but my phone client app could not subscribe to that layer. If I use a layer created by a user, the bridge can't connect. I was passing the application access token from the phone to the bridge API, then passing it to geoloqi in my message/broadcast call.&nbsp;</div><div><br /></div><div>There has to be a way to do this. If not, I think my only alternative is to allow each user to create their own layer on which they can create places etc, and have each user subscribe to all layers in the app.&nbsp;</div><div><br /></div><div>Any suggestions?</div><div><br /></div><div>Thanks,</div><div>Bruce</div>]]></description>
   </item>
   <item>
      <title>Need api help for geoloqi - get users between two locations</title>
      <link>http://community.geoloqi.com/discussion/166/need-api-help-for-geoloqi-get-users-between-two-locations</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 08:07:48 -0800</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>vividcode</dc:creator>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">166@/discussions</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Everyone,<br /><br />I am new to geoloqi platform.<br />My client want an iPhone app developed based on geoloqi.<br /><br />I have already downloaded some <a rel="nofollow" href="https://github.com/geoloqi">iOS samples</a> from github which shows some uses of api.<br /><br />The requirement is:<br /><br />a) Ability to get all user's list going from place A to place B<br />b) Ability to send messages to nearby users<br />c) Ability to have voice sessions with users<br /><br />Out of the above, a) is very mandatory - purpose of the app.<br />I see <a rel="nofollow" href="http://developers.geoloqi.com/api">api </a>but can't find anything that will give me users' list based on location.<br /><br />Since this is very crucial to decide whether to use geoloqi or not, I need urgent help.<br /><br />Could anyone show me the way or show an example where this is used? Most favorably an open source?<br /><br />Many thanks for reading and trying to help...<br />-vividCode<br /><br /><br />]]></description>
   </item>
   <item>
      <title>SMS from Geonotes?</title>
      <link>http://community.geoloqi.com/discussion/157/sms-from-geonotes</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2012 13:30:58 -0800</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FFuAP1isUgmzsz7KX</dc:creator>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">157@/discussions</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[I have had success sending push notifications using Geonotes. Is it possible to use Geonotes to send SMS messages? Or is that only available through the API?<div><br /></div><div>Thanks,</div><div><br /></div><div>BC</div>]]></description>
   </item>
   <item>
      <title>Best practices for Offline App</title>
      <link>http://community.geoloqi.com/discussion/134/best-practices-for-offline-app</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 03:46:58 -0700</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>wisepilgrim</dc:creator>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">134@/discussions</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Hey folks, new to the forums but a relatively experienced titanium developer interested in the opportunities that Geoloqi presents.<br /><br />My questions is to do with the offline use of Geoloqi's features.&nbsp; I would like to build a set of apps geared towards tourists who are traveling without a data plan.&nbsp; <br /><br />Can anybody suggest a few bullet points as to how I can implement such a task?&nbsp; Data could be downloaded periodically via wifi, but the notifications would need to appear while they were actually walking and offline.<br /><br />Doable?<br />]]></description>
   </item>
   <item>
      <title>Create layers places and triggers using the application token with the Android SDK</title>
      <link>http://community.geoloqi.com/discussion/149/create-layers-places-and-triggers-using-the-application-token-with-the-android-sdk</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 10:22:13 -0800</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>itaybiri</dc:creator>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">149@/discussions</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Hey,<div><br /></div><div>I am using the default creation of anon users whenever my application starts.</div><div>Once a user does an action on the phone I would like to create a Layer, Place, Trigger and subscribe other users for that layer in order for them to get notifications.&nbsp;<span>I am using the Android SDK so after binding the service I take the LQSession and run the creation and subscription requests with it.</span></div><div>As far as I understand and see on the debugger I am creating them using the user's key but I actually need to create them using the application key ( I even get an access denied when subscribing the users to the created layer). How do I create them with the application key using the SDK and am I doing anything wrong ??</div><div><br /></div><div>Thanks a lot!</div>]]></description>
   </item>
   <item>
      <title>Is there a better way to know that LQSession was created?</title>
      <link>http://community.geoloqi.com/discussion/145/is-there-a-better-way-to-know-that-lqsession-was-created</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2012 17:53:41 -0800</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>95JmV1ipaHHWcjRac</dc:creator>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">145@/discussions</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[I did not find any listeners in LQService in sdk for android.<br />Now when i have a first run of the service, it creates anonymous user account automatically, and i do not need to call function "LQSession.createAnonymousUserAccount" again for it.<br /><br /><p><span><span>How can i check, that anonymous user was created (or how i can disable it automatically creation at first start)?</span></span> Now i use this java code (but i hope that better way is exists):</p><p>// at this point i have a started LQService</p><p><img src="http://community.geoloqi.com/uploads/FileUpload/b0/bd20c7d26c094b0e06722b546d0d80.png" alt="image" /></p>]]></description>
   </item>
   <item>
      <title>Location update</title>
      <link>http://community.geoloqi.com/discussion/144/location-update</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2012 16:27:30 -0800</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>95JmV1ipaHHWcjRac</dc:creator>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">144@/discussions</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Is it possible  to update locations for all anonymous users that associated with one device_id in android and ios?<br /></p>]]></description>
   </item>
   <item>
      <title>API limits</title>
      <link>http://community.geoloqi.com/discussion/118/api-limits</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2012 01:46:29 -0700</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Martz256</dc:creator>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">118@/discussions</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Hi,<div><br /></div><div>I am really interested in using GeoLoqi but am having a lot of trouble understanding which package i need.</div><div><br /></div><div>I don't need to use any GeoTriggers at this time and purely want to use geoloqi to track the apps position and use the API calls to receive information. As far as i can see this is not a paid service and essentially I could use unlimited api calls on the free egg package?</div><div><br /></div><div>However i can't find this information anywhere and would hate to submit my app to the app store only to be told that i face a large bill or that my app is taken offline as i don't have the correct package.</div><div><br /></div><div>Can anyone help with a little info?</div><div><br /></div><div>thanks</div>]]></description>
   </item>
   <item>
      <title>Custom web interface</title>
      <link>http://community.geoloqi.com/discussion/117/custom-web-interface</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2012 05:08:43 -0700</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>acastro917</dc:creator>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">117@/discussions</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Hi, I'm writing a project to my developer and would like to use Geologi for this hoping I can get what I want.&nbsp; At the begging was only to provide a custom FIND MY PHONE version to be implemented on my web and my app user, now that I found Geologi plans has change a lot.<br /><br />I provide&nbsp; a software to my clients freight forwarder and carriers around the world but mostly to serve Latin America, now I want to offer more control over their drivers and since they are using my mobile APP (IOS) I guess is just some integration.<br /><br />So far the basic Idea is create a site like yours where clients can do what I do create place, notes, send instant messages to specific user etc.<br /><br />My client has a list of driver and he can create this note, places for individual and for groups...?<br /><br />Way to my user see their stats usage.. since I will be charging for this services would like to offer a view where their money goes..?<br /><br />History way to play back what each driver did, time stop, etc...<br /><br />any help highly appreciated<br /><br /><br /><br /><br />]]></description>
   </item>
   <item>
      <title>Streaming and Share Token</title>
      <link>http://community.geoloqi.com/discussion/106/streaming-and-share-token</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 16:20:31 -0700</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>JYPR1ijMckK1uqCv</dc:creator>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">106@/discussions</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Hi<div><br /></div><div>I am new to Geoloqi development and will be wanting to use the streaming functionality of the api.</div><div><br /></div><div>Reading the documentation it says:</div><div><br /></div><div><i>When users are sharing their location with a share token, you can use that token to see their position in real time, same as with groups.</i></div><div><i><br /></i></div><div>I am having trouble finding what a share token is. &nbsp;Is this the same as a user's access token? if not, do you use the share token when saving the user's location with "location/update"? &nbsp;Is there a good example that displays this functionality including the creation/retrieval/use of the share token?</div><div><br /></div><div>I'm using the javascript-client api.</div><div><br /></div><div>Thanks</div>]]></description>
   </item>
   <item>
      <title>iOS: Get the trigger_id from push notification?</title>
      <link>http://community.geoloqi.com/discussion/104/ios-get-the-trigger_id-from-push-notification</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2012 02:14:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>cKDVB1iU1UMG2Zvri</dc:creator>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">104@/discussions</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Whenever I receive a push notification, I would like to know what was the "trigger" for that push notification. Is this possible?&nbsp;<div><br /></div><div>I got this from -application:didReceiveRemoteNotification:</div><div><br /></div><div><br /><br /><p class="p1">/+[LQSession handlePush:] (LQSession.m:138) Push Notification Received: {</p><br /><p class="p1">&nbsp; &nbsp; aps = &nbsp; &nbsp; {</p><br /><p class="p1">&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; alert = &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; {</p><br /><p class="p1">&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; "action-loc-key" = "&lt;null&gt;";</p><br /><p class="p1">&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; body = "My saved memo location notification";</p><br /><p class="p1">&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; };</p><br /><p class="p1">&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; sound = default;</p><br /><p class="p1">&nbsp; &nbsp; };</p><br /><p class="p1">&nbsp; &nbsp; geoloqi = &nbsp; &nbsp; {</p><br /><p class="p1">&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; token = 4CAbTTkb4nF;</p><br /><p class="p1">&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; type = message;</p><br /><p class="p1">&nbsp; &nbsp; };</p><br /><p class="p1">}</p><p class="p1"><br /></p><p class="p1">I believe the token is not the trigger id. I'm not sure how I would use that.</p><p class="p1">TIA!</p></div>]]></description>
   </item>
   <item>
      <title>How to use the application access token?</title>
      <link>http://community.geoloqi.com/discussion/57/how-to-use-the-application-access-token</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2012 19:01:05 -0700</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>pluggedin</dc:creator>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57@/discussions</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Good day,<div><br /></div><div>I am trying to use the application token to access the layers set up for it, but I can't understand where to use the application access token. For example, sending a request like this -&nbsp;</div><div><span class="Apple-style-span"><span>[[</span><span>LQSession</span><span> </span><span>savedSession</span><span>] </span><span>requestWithMethod</span><span>:</span>@"GET"<span> </span><span>path</span><span>:</span>@"/place/list?oauth_token=APPLICATIONTOKEN"<span> </span><span>payload</span><span>:[</span><span>NSDictionary</span><span> </span><span>dictionaryWithObjectsAndKeys</span><span>:</span><span>nil</span><span>]];</span></span></div><div><span class="Apple-style-span"><span><br /></span></span></div><div>I get an error - "<span class="Apple-style-span">Auth token found in GET or POST when token also present in header"</span></div><div><span class="Apple-style-span"><br /></span></div><div><span class="Apple-style-span"><span class="Apple-style-span">It seems that I need to change the auth token used somewhere else, but I can't find where to do that.</span></span></div><div><span class="Apple-style-span"><span class="Apple-style-span"><br /></span></span></div><div>Any help would be appreciated. Thanks.</div>]]></description>
   </item>
   <item>
      <title>place/nearby latitude and longitude</title>
      <link>http://community.geoloqi.com/discussion/25/placenearby-latitude-and-longitude</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 17:05:36 -0800</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>ByKKi1hPy8ZkNypyq</dc:creator>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25@/discussions</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Hello.<br />At <a href="http://developers.geoloqi.com/api/place/nearby" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://developers.geoloqi.com/api/place/nearby</a> I see that longitude and latitude are optional, but no matter do I pass them or not, I am always getting following response:<br />{"error_code":400,"error":"missing_input","error_description":"Latitude and longitude are required"}<br />Am I missing something?<br />]]></description>
   </item>
   <item>
      <title>See a list of geonotes made</title>
      <link>http://community.geoloqi.com/discussion/24/see-a-list-of-geonotes-made</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2012 00:19:26 -0800</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>SZgoW1hSMXvUuGnU0</dc:creator>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24@/discussions</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hi</p><br /><p>I'm very new to the app and wanted to know if there's a&nbsp;a way of seeing&nbsp;a geonote&nbsp;on the map once I've made it? I'd like to be able to edit a note and can't at the moment see how to do that.</p><br /><p>Apologies in advance for being dumb if the answer is very obvious!</p><br /><p>Ian</p>]]></description>
   </item>
   <item>
      <title>Is there a way to export tracks?</title>
      <link>http://community.geoloqi.com/discussion/11/is-there-a-way-to-export-tracks</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2011 21:16:12 -0700</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>geografa</dc:creator>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11@/discussions</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Is this better accomplished through the Instamapper API? Being able to export a GPX, CSV, or KML of the tracks would be useful.]]></description>
   </item>
   <item>
      <title>Can I export all my location data?</title>
      <link>http://community.geoloqi.com/discussion/22/can-i-export-all-my-location-data</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2011 18:54:35 -0800</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>aaronpk</dc:creator>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">22@/discussions</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<div>Yes! You can use our API to download all your GPS data.&nbsp;</div><div><br /></div><div>The way this works is to download your history in batches of about 1,000 to 10,000 points.</div><div><br /></div><div>Here are the parameters you'll need to set. You can find the full API documentation here:&nbsp;<a href="http://developers.geoloqi.com/api/location/history" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://developers.geoloqi.com/api/location/history</a></div><div><ul><li><span style="font-family: 'Courier New';">count = 1000 or 10000</span>. Try both and see which you like better.</li><li><span style="font-family: 'Courier New';">accuracy = 10000</span>. This will include the extremely rough cell tower updates that come in at about 1500m accuracy.</li><li><span style="font-family: 'Courier New';">ignore_gaps = 1</span>. This will prevent the API from returning only the latest trip it finds, and will instead return all data even if there are large gaps in time</li><li><span style="font-family: 'Courier New';">after =&nbsp;0000000000</span>, or the first date you have recorded data</li></ul></div><div>When you run that you will get a large JSON document with the keys&nbsp;<span style="font-family: 'courier new', monospace;">points</span>,&nbsp;<span style="font-family: 'courier new', monospace;">distance</span>,&nbsp;<span style="font-family: 'courier new', monospace;">timerange</span>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<span style="font-family: 'courier new', monospace;">bounds</span>. The location data is in the&nbsp;<span style="font-family: 'courier new', monospace;">points</span>&nbsp;array. To continue fetching data, use the value in&nbsp;<span style="font-family: 'courier new', monospace;">timerange.to_ts</span>&nbsp;as the value for "after" in the next API call.</div><div><br /></div>Eventually you will end up iterating to the current time and you'll get an empty array for "points".&nbsp;<div><br /></div><div><span>You can see some short code examples and you can get a permanent access token on the&nbsp;</span><a rel="nofollow" href="http://developers.geoloqi.com/getting-started">Getting Started</a><span>&nbsp;page.</span><br /></div><div><span><br /></span></div>]]></description>
   </item>
   <item>
      <title>Can I add a KML-file as layer on the Google map with the embed code?</title>
      <link>http://community.geoloqi.com/discussion/9/can-i-add-a-kml-file-as-layer-on-the-google-map-with-the-embed-code</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2011 21:10:41 -0700</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>fverpoest</dc:creator>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9@/discussions</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Hi,<br />I want to add a KML file on my map that I embed on my homepage.<br />I walk a 100km-route and use Geoloqi send my current location. It will be nice, if people se the entire route that I must walk.<br />Can I add code to include a KLM file with the route in the Google-map?<br /><br />Grtz, <br />Fred<br /><br />]]></description>
   </item>
   <item>
      <title>Recording a route and playing it back?</title>
      <link>http://community.geoloqi.com/discussion/10/recording-a-route-and-playing-it-back</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2011 21:12:36 -0700</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>PhillWilson2</dc:creator>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10@/discussions</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[I am a rural mail carrier. I have to work different routes sometimes. If I could record the route and then have it play back, with notes on turnarounds and vacant boxes this would be great. Any ideas?]]></description>
   </item>
   </channel>
</rss>